

LISA CHATELLIER

WEB DEVELOPER JUNIOR

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptation
- Team player
- Autonomy
- Communication
 Good analytical
 - skills
 - Curiosity
 - Patience

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby
- Rails
- HTML5
- CSS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- PostgreSQL
- Heroku
- GitHub
- Git
- Cloudinary

FIND ME AT:

Cell: +33 6 3619 4556 Email: lisachatellier90@gmail.com GitHub: shinboram-90 LinkedIn: lisa-chatellier



www.lisachatellier.com



GET TO KNOW ME

After 10 years in the hospitality industry, I decided to make a career transition to web development and that's how I started "Le Wagon" (Bordeaux, France) coding bootcamp earlier this year.

I became very passionate about programming and I would like to grow my skills and keep learning new technologies. In order to do so, I'm currently looking for a company offering a 1-year sandwich course with the French online professional training platform: "OpenClassrooms".



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sales Assistant

NEXITY, JUNE 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

- Sales prospecting calls to clients interested in renting a property
- Planning visits of the properties in coordination with the real estate agents' schedule
- Entering reservations and rental applications in the system

Guest Service Agent & HR Administrator

ACCOR, MARCH 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

- Assisted with the onboarding of new employees including contracts
- Provided exceptional customer service by responding to guest requests promptly, efficiently and courteously during check-in, check-out and throughout their stay



EDUCATION

Le Wagon Bordeaux

BOOTCAMP FULL-STACK, APRIL 2021 - JUNE 2021

- 9-week Ruby on Rails focused coding bootcamp
- Building 2 web applications from scratch in team of 3:
- "A day in a movie": inspired by "AirBnb"
- "Woodstock": website allowing to tailor a piece of furniture in 3D using ThreeJs

Excelia La Rochelle

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN TOURISM & HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT. 2014-2016

- Graduated with honorable mention
- Specializations: Asian region, Hospitality Management & E-Marketing
- 2nd year in English language track including 1 semester exchange program at Jeju National University (Jeju, South Korea)
- 3rd year on sandwich course training with Appart'hôtel Odalys Archipel (La Rochelle, France)



I'm a globe-trotter who doesn't hesitate to fly to the other side of the world alone in order to discover new cultures but also to get out of my comfort zone.

Trully passionate about everything I do, I'm fond of music (playing piano and guitar), go game, Korean cuisine, scuba-diving and of course coding!